{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Genocide' means--------",
      "answer": "mass murder",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "mass murder",
        "a type of parasites",
        "musical instrument",
        "systematic cultivation"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing one self",
      "answer": "suicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["suicide", "Patricide", "Matricide", " Fratricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing father",
      "answer": "Patricide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Patricide", "suicide", "Matricide", " Fratricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing mother",
      "answer": "Matricide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Matricide", "Patricide", " Fratricide", "Matricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing brother",
      "answer": " Fratricide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [" Fratricide", "Sororicide", "Parenticide", "Viricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing  sister",
      "answer": "Sororicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Sororicide", " Fratricide", "Viricide", "Parenticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing Parents",
      "answer": "Parenticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Parenticide", "Sororicide", " Fratricide", "Viricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing husband",
      "answer": "Viricide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Viricide", "Parenticide", "Sororicide", " Fratricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing wife",
      "answer": "Uxoricide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Uxoricide", "Filicide", "Prolicide", "Parricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing son",
      "answer": "Filicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Filicide", "Uxoricide", "Prolicide", "Parricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing daughter",
      "answer": "Prolicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Prolicide", "Filicide", "Uxoricide", "Parricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing close relatives",
      "answer": "Parricide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Parricide", "Prolicide", "Filicide", "Uxoricide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a man or any person",
      "answer": "Homicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Homicide", "Killing a woman", "Infanticide", "Aborticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a woman",
      "answer": "Killing a woman",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Killing a woman", "Homicide", "Aborticide", "Infanticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing an infant",
      "answer": "Infanticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Infanticide", "Killing a woman", "Homicide", "Aborticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a foetus",
      "answer": "Aborticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Aborticide", "Senicide", "Regicide", "Philosophicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing an oldmen",
      "answer": "Senicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Senicide", "Aborticide", "Philosophicide", "Regicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a king",
      "answer": "Regicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Regicide", "Senicide", "Aborticide", "Philosophicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing Philosopher",
      "answer": "Philosophicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Philosophicide", "Regicide", "Senicide", "Aborticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a poet",
      "answer": "Vaticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Vaticide", "episcopicscide", "Brahminicide", "nepoticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing of bishop",
      "answer": "episcopicscide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["episcopicscide", "Vaticide", "nepoticide", "Brahminicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a Brahmin",
      "answer": "Brahminicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Brahminicide", "nepoticide", "Ambicide", "Hosticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a favourite",
      "answer": "nepoticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["nepoticide", "Brahminicide", "Hosticide", "Ambicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a friend",
      "answer": "Ambicide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Ambicide", "nepoticide", "Brahminicide", "Hosticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing an enemy",
      "answer": "Hosticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Hosticide", "tyranticide", "Hospiticide", "Regicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing tyrant",
      "answer": "tyranticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["tyranticide", "Hosticide", "Regicide", "Hospiticide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Killing a guest",
      "answer": "Hospiticide",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Hospiticide", "tyranticide", "Hosticide", "Regicide"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The one word substitute for an unmarried woman.",
      "answer": "spinster",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["spinster", "lady", "mistress", "bachelor"]
    },
    {
      "question": "a woman just before her wedding day, a newly married women",
      "answer": "bride",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bride", "bridegroom", "endogamy", "fiance"]
    },
    {
      "question": "a man just before his wedding day, a newly married man",
      "answer": "bridegroom",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bridegroom", "bride", "fiance", "endogamy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "marrying only within the tribe",
      "answer": "endogamy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["endogamy", "bridegroom", "bride", "fiance"]
    },
    {
      "question": "a man to whom a girl is engaged to be married",
      "answer": "fiance",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["fiance", "endogamy", "bridegroom", "bride"]
    },
    {
      "question": "a girl to whom a man is engaged to be married",
      "answer": "Fiancee",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Fiancee", "Polyandry", "Polygami", "Celibacy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The practice of having more than one husband at the same time",
      "answer": "Polyandry",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Polyandry", "Fiancee", "Celibacy", "Polygami"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The practice of having more than one wives at the same time",
      "answer": "Polygami",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Polygami", "Celibacy", "Bigami", "Monogamy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being umarried",
      "answer": "Celibacy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Celibacy", "Polygami", "Monogamy", "Bigami"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The state of having two wives or husbands at the same time",
      "answer": "Bigami",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Bigami", "Monogamy", "Celibacy", "Polygami"]
    },
    {
      "question": "only one wife",
      "answer": "Monogamy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Monogamy", "Bigami", "Polygami", "Celibacy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The property which women bring at marriage.",
      "answer": "Dowry",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Dowry", "Widow", "Widower", "Diagamy"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A woman whose husband is dead.",
      "answer": "Widow",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Widow", "Dowry", "Diagamy", "Widower"]
    },
    {
      "question": "a man whose wife is dead",
      "answer": "Widower",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Widower", "Diagamy", "Spouse", "Dowry"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Second marriage",
      "answer": "Diagamy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Diagamy", "Widower", "Spouse", "Dowry"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Husband/ wife",
      "answer": "Spouse",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["Spouse", "Diagamy", "Widower", "Dowry"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The hundredth anniversary of a significant event is called ---------",
      "answer": "centuary",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["centuary", "centenary", "sanctuary", "sentuary"]
    }
  ]
}
